Guide to the Health Systems Agency of Southwestern Pennsylvania Records, 1971-1987 AIS.1987.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Projects, 1971-1987; I.
  - 1380-Southern Indiana Medical Center--Community Health Center Grant Application, 1984
  - 1381-Commonwealth of Pennsylvania--Black Lung Clinics Program, 1984
  - 1382-Eye and Ear/Presbyterian-University Hospital--Ambulatory Surgical Facility, 1984
  - 1383-Mercy Hospital of Pittsburgh--Conversion of 6 Medical/Surgical Beds to Comprehensive Medical Rehabilitation Beds, 1984
  - 1384-Sewickley Valley Hospital--Replacement of Fluoroscopic Equipment, 1984 (Box 209)
  - 1385-Braddock General Hospital--Convert 2 Medical/Surgical Beds to Psychiatric Beds, 1984
  - 1386-McKeesport Hospital--Renovation of OB and Pediatric Units, 1984
  - 1387-Mobile Imaging--Provide Mobile CT Scanning Services to Harmarville Rehab Center, 1984
  - 1388-Health Care Industries-Sycamore Creek Nursing Home--Addition of 1 Bed, 1984
  - 1389-Washington County Health Center--Correction of Structural Deficiencies, 1984
  - 1390-Allegheny County Health Department--Injury Prevention Demonstration Program in an Economically Depressed Community, 1984
  - 1391-Greensburg North Associates--Cost Increase on Hopehill Nursing Home, 1984
  - 1392-Dialysis Clinics of New Kensington--Addition of 1 ESRD Station, 1984
  - 1393-Forbes Regional Health Center--Addition of 10 Medical/Surgical Beds, 1984
  - 1394-Forbes Health System--Computerized Information System, 1984
  - 1395-Community Development Centers--Relocate 132 ICF/MR Beds to Community Group Homes, 1985 (Box 210)
  - 1396-Jeannette District Memorial Hospital--Acquire a Full Body CT Scanner, 1984
  - 1397-Centerville Clinics--Rural Health Initiative, 1985
  - 1398-Frank Stanish, M.D.--Establish an Ambulatory Surgical Facility, 1984
  - 1399-McMurray Hills Manor--Addition of 10 LTC Beds, 1984
  - 1400-Regency Hall Nursing Home--Addition of 2 LTC Beds, 1984
  - 1401-West Allegheny Hospital--Addition of 9 Medical/Surgical Beds, 1984
  - 1402-Alma Illery Medical Center--Community Health Services Continuation Grant Application, 1984
  - 1403-Mercy Hospital--Construction and Renovation, 1985 (Box 211)
  - 1404-SE/Greene Community Health Centers--Community Health Center Continuation Grant Application, 1984
  - 1405-Dialysis Clinics of Aliquippa--Addition of 1 ESRD Station, 1984
  - 1406-Medical Center of Beaver County--Establish a Drug and Alcohol Rehab Program, 1984
  - 1407-West Penn Hospital--Redistribution of Beds, 1984
  - 1408-Baptist Homes of Western Pennsylvania--Change in Project Cost, 1984
  - 1409-Uniontown Hospital--Construction/Renovation, 1985
  - 1410-South Hills Health System--Free-Standing Ambulatory Surgical Facility on the Jefferson Hospital Campus, 1984
  - 1411-Westmoreland Hospital Association--Establish a Drug/Alcohol Detoxification/Rehabilitation Unit, 1984 (Box 212)
  - 1412-Forbes Health System--Debt Refinancing, 1984
  - 1413-Laurel Rest Home--Addition of 5 Beds, 1984
  - 1414-Montefiore Hospital--Construction of Additional Office Space, 1984
  - 1415-St. Francis Medical Center--Acquisition of an Extracorporeal Shock Wave Lithotripter Device, 1985
  - 1416-Armstrong County Memorial Hospital--Replace CT Scanner, 1984
  - 1417-Allegheny General Hospital--Replacement of Neuroangiography Equipment, 1984
  - 1418-Allegheny Valley Hospital--Addition of 10 Medical/Surgical Beds, 1984
  - 1419-Magee-Women's Hospital--Replace Telecommunications System, 1985
  - 1420-The Washington Hospital--Construction/Renovation Program, 1984 (Box 213)
  - 1421-St.Joseph Nursing and Health Care Center--Addition of 6 Skilled Beds, 1984
  - 1422-St. Francis Medical Center--Debt Refinancing, 1985
  - 1423-Hartwood Health Center--200-Bed LTC Facility in Northeast Allegheny County, 1984
  - 1424-BMA of Southwestern PA--Addition of 1 Dialysis Station, 1984
  - 1425-Champ Development--Cost Increase on Rochester Manor, 1985
  - 1426-St. Margaret Memorial Hospital--Installation of a Whole House Data Processing System, 1985
  - 1427-Indiana Hospital--Designate 20 Medical/Surgical Beds as Ambulatory Surgical Unit, 1984
  - 1428-Allegheny General Hospital--Provision of Renal Transplant Services, 1985 (Box 214)
  - 1429-Shannock Valley Area Medical Facility--RHI Continuation Grant Application, 1985
  - 1430-St. Francis Medical Center--Change in Scope, 1985
  - 1431-Rehab Hospital Services Corporation--Cost Increase, 1985
  - 1432-NE/Butler County Community Medical Center--RHI Continuation Grant Application, 1985
  - 1433-Shadyside Hospital--Addition of 10 Medical/Surgical Beds, 1985
  - 1434-Shadyside Hospital--Addition of Cardiac Catheterization Lab, 1985
  - 1435-F.O.R.-Sto-Rox Neighborhood Corp.--Urban Health Initiative, 1985
  - 1436-University Health Center of Pittsburgh--Replace Telecommunications System, 1985
  - 1437-St. Johns General Hospital--Addition of 7 Psychiatric Beds, 1985
  - 1438-BMA of Pittsburgh--Addition of 2 Dialysis Stations, 1985
  - 1439-Butler Memorial Hospital--Construction of Acute Care Hospital in Southwest Butler County, 1985
  - 1440-Jeannette District Memorial Hospital--Decrease OB Beds by 12 and Designate 18 Medical/Surgical Beds for Intermediate Rehab Unit, 1985 (Box 215)
  - 1441-Voluntary Hospitals of America--Purchase of ESWL Equipment and Renovation of Space for the Equipment, 1985
  - 1442-Southwestern Nursing and Rehab Center--A 120-Bed LTC Facility in Pleasant Hills, 1985
  - 1443-Magee Women's Hospital--Refinancing of Long-Term Debt, 1985
  - 1444-West Penn Hospital--Digital Subtraction Angiography, 1985
  - 1445-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Development of Stereotactic Radiosurgery, 1985
  - 1446-Manor Health Care Corporation--Cost Increase on Leader Nursing and Rehab Center of Bethel Park, 1985
  - 1447-Kane Regional Centers--Advanced Refunding of Bonds, 1985
  - 1448-Braddock General Hospital--Addition of 6 Psychiatric Beds, 1985 (Box 216)
  - 1449-Visiting Nurse Association of Western Pennsylvania--Homemaker/Home Health Aide Training Programs, 1985
  - 1450-Mobile Diagnostic Services--Provide Mobile CT Scanning Services to Greene County Memorial Hospital, 1985
  - 1451-Community Medical Center of Northwest Washington County--Rural Health Initiative, 1985
  - 1452-Allegheny General Hospital--Construct a 1200 Unit Parking Garage, 1985
  - 1453-Montefiore Hospital, Establishment of an Extracorporeal Shock Wave Lithotripsy Service, 1985
  - 1454-Episcopal Church Home--Renovation and Expansion Project, 1985
  - 1455-The South Side Hospital--Refinancing of Long-Term Debt, 1985
  - 1456-Monongahela Valley Hospital--Replacement of CT Scanner, 1985 (Box 217)
  - 1457-West Penn Hospital--Establish an Inpatient Psych Unit, Convert Medical/Surgical Beds to Psych, 1985
  - 1458-Regency Hall Nursing Home--Addition of 8 Skilled Beds, 1985
  - 1459-Emery Medical Management Company--Construct 200-Bed LTC Facility, 1985
  - 1460-Montefiore Hospital, Cardiovascular Surgery expansion, 1985
  - 1461-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Develop an Ambulatory Surgical Facility, 1985
  - 1462-Tri-State Lithotriptic Institute--Acquisition of an ESWL Device, 1985
  - 1463-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Replacement of Cardiac Catheterization Laboratory, 1985
  - 1464-AMI Diagnostic Services--Provide Mobile CT Scanning Services to Brownsville General Hospital, St. Johns General Hospital and Union City Memorial Hospital, 1985 (Box 218)
  - 1465-Jameson Memorial Hospital--Debt Refinancing, 1985
  - 1466-West View Care Center--Addition of 2 Beds, 1985
  - 1467-RMA of South Hills--Addition of 1 Dialysis Station, 1985
  - 1468-St. Margaret Memorial Hospital--Debt Refinancing, 1985
  - 1469-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Hyperbaric Oxygen Therapy Program, 1985
  - 1470-Forbes Regional Health Center--Replace CT Scanner, 1985
  - 1471-Health Center Development--Advance Refunding of Long-Term Debt, 1985
  - 1472-Manor Health Care Corporation--Cost Increase of Leader Nursing and Rehabilitation Center of Scott Township, 1985
  - 1473-Medical Center of Beaver County--Renovation and Reduction of 11 Medical/Surgical Beds, 1985
  - 1474-Eye and Ear Hospital--Develop an Ambulatory Surgical Facility, 1985 (Box 219)
  - 1475-SE/Greene Community Health Center--Community Health Center Continuation Grant Application, 1985
  - 1476-Centerville Clinics--Rural Health Initiative, 1985
  - 1477-Apollo Medical Foundation--Rural Health Initiative, 1985
  - 1478-Canonsburg General Hospital--Provide Mobile CT-Scanning Services to West Allegheny Hospital, 1985
  - 1479-Primary Care Health Services--Community Health Services, 1985
  - 1480-Pennsylvania Department of Health--Immunization Program Grant Application, 1985
  - 1481-St. Clair Memorial Hospital--Advance Refunding of Bonds, 1984
  - 1482-Belvedere Residence --Construct a 15-Bed Intermediate Care Facility, 1985
  - 1483-Westmoreland Hospital Association--Refinancing of Current Bond Issue, 1985
  - 1484-Southwest Health System--Bond Issue, 1985
  - 1485-Montefiore Hospital--Debt Refinancing, 1985 (Box 220)
  - 1486-West Penn Hospital--Advance Refunding of Hospital Bonds, 1985
  - 1487-Westview Care Center--Addition of Beds and Renovation, 1985
  - 1488-Community Dialysis Services of McKeesport--Addition of Five Dialysis Stations, 1985
  - 1489-RMA of Greensburg--Addition of One Dialysis Station, 1985
  - 1490-The South Side Hospital--Renovate Former Nursing School and Upgrade Parking, 1985
  - 1491-Children's Hospital--Refinance Outstanding Bond Issue, 1985
  - 1492-Allegheny General Hospital--Transfer of Six Renal Dialysis Stations, 1985
  - 1493-St. Margaret Memorial Hospital--Finance Long-Range Capital Expenditure, 1985
  - 1494-Bio-Medical Application--10-Station ESRD Facility in North Hills, 1985
  - 1495-St. Francis Medical Center--Hyperbaric Chamber and Ventilator, 1985
  - 1496-Greenville Orthopedic Association/Ambulatory Surgical Care Corporation--3 Operating Rooms, Free-Standing A.S.F. in Barkeyville, 1985
  - 1497-Medical Center of Beaver County--Cancer Treatment Center Improvement Program, 1985
  - 1498-Allegheny General Hospital--Educational Conference Center, 1985 (Box 221)
  - 1499-Montefiore Hospital--Acquisition of Dual Place Hyperbaric Chamber, 1985
  - 1500-Shadyside Hospital--Replace Data Processing System, 1985
  - 1501-Bio-Medical Applications--Establish an Eleven Station Outpatient Dialysis Facility, 1986
  - 1502-Allegheny Valley Hospital--Replace CT Scanner, 1986
  - 1503-Allegheny General Hospital--Hyperbaric Oxygen Services, 1986
  - 1504-Westmoreland Manor--Incinerator Waste Heat Boiler Plant, 1986
  - 1505-St. Margaret Memorial Hospital--Cost Overrun on Ambulatory Surgery Facility, 1986
  - 1506-Shannock Valley Area Medical Facility--Continued Funding, 1986
  - 1507-Northeast Butler County Community Medical Center--Continuation Application, 1986
  - 1508-Evergreen Convalescent Home--Replace and Expand Existing Facility, 1986
  - 1509-Sherwood Oaks--Refinancing Long Term Bonds, 1986 (Box 222)
  - 1510-F.O.R. Sto-Rox Neighborhood Family Health Center--Continuation Grant Application, 1986
  - 1511-Family Planning Council of Western Pennsylvania--Continuation Grant Application, 1986
  - 1512-Dialysis Clinics--Increase Stations in Aliquippa Facility From 12 to 16 Stations, 1986
  - 1513-McKeesport Hospital--Acquisition of a Replacement Linear Accelerator, 1986
  - 1514-Medical Center of Beaver County--Cancer Treatment Linear Accelerator, 1986
  - 1515-Commonwealth of Pennsylvania--Acquired Immunodeficiency Syndrome/Health Education and Risk Reduction Program, 1986
  - 1516-St. Francis Medical Center--Refinance Bond Issue to Fixed Rate Debt, 1986
  - 1517-Citizens General Hospital--Replace CT Scanner, 1986
  - 1518-Pennsylvania Dialysis Clinics--Establish a 10 Station Dialysis Facility in New Castle, 1986
  - 1519-Latrobe Area Hospital--Expand and Upgrade Facilities, 1986
  - 1520-West Virginia Health Care Cooperative--8 Station Renal Dialysis Center in Uniontown, 1986
  - 1521-Community Medical Center of Northwestern Washington County--RHI Continuation Application, 1986 (Box 223)
  - 1522-Sewickley Valley Hospital--Medical Office Building, 1986
  - 1523-The Western Pennsylvania Hospital--Refinancing of Existing Long-Term Debt, 1986
  - 1524-Westmoreland Hospital/Gateway--Substance Abuse Rehabilitation Program, 1986
  - 1525-Bio-Medical Applications--Establish a 10-Station Freestanding Dialysis Facility in Uniontown, 1986
  - 1526-West Penn MRI Institute--Provision of Magnetic Resonance Imaging Service, 1986
  - 1527-Civic Dialysis Services--Establish a 10-Station ESRD Facility in Southeastern Pittsburgh, 1986
  - 1528-St. Clair Memorial Hospital--Addition of Two Floors to Parking Garage, 1986
  - 1529-St. Clair Memorial Hospital--Develop a 40-Bed Psychiatric Hospital, 1986 (Box 224)
  - 1530-Triangle Radiation Oncology Associates--Provision of Cancer Treatment Services to Inpatients, 1986
  - 1531-Mayview State Hospital--Install Air-Conditioning System, 1986
  - 1532-Westmoreland Hospital--Addition of Linear Accelerator, 1986
  - 1533-St. Francis Medical Center--Replace 25 MeV Betatron Machine with Dual-Energy Linear Accelerator, 1986
  - 1534-Butler Memorial Hospital--Refinancing Existing Debt for Previously Approved Project, 1986
  - 1535-Allegheny Health Services, Montefiore & St. Francis Hospitals, Extracorporeal Shock Wave Lithotripsy service, 1986-1987
  - 1536-Divine Providence Hospital--Cost Increase on Project, 1986
  - 1537-Commonwealth of Pennsylvania--Black Lung Clinics Program, 1986
  - 1538-Shadyside Hospital--Establish MRI Services, 1986
  - 1539-Commonwealth of Pennsylvania--Venereal Disease Control Grant Application, 1986 (Box 225)
  - 1540-Visiting Nurse Association--Homemaker/Home Health Aide Training Programs, 1986
  - 1541-Health Center Development--Acquire Magnetic Resonance Imager, 1986
  - 1542-The Washington Hospital--C.T. Scanner Replacement, 1986
  - 1543-Montefiore Hospital--Acquire Magnetic Resonance Imager, 1986
  - 1544-Cameron Company Health Care Center--Rural Health Initiative, 1986
  - 1545-Armstrong County Memorial Hospital--Acquisition of a Linear Accelerator and Simulator, 1986
  - 1546-Woodville State Hospital--Program and Budget for 1987/1988 Fiscal Year, 1986
  - 1547-Planning and Development of MRI Center--St. Clair/South Hills H.S./South Side Hospitals, 1986
  - 1548-Allegheny Health Services--Replacement Management Information System, 1986
  - 1549-South Hills Health System--Cost Increase on Ambulatory Surgical Facility, 1986
  - 1550-Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, Grant Application for Immunization, 1987
  - 1551-Allegheny Valley Hospital--Refinancing Existing Bond Issue, 1986 (Box 226)
  - 1552-Valley Community Services--Develop an ICF/MR Facility, 1986
  - 1553-St. John Lutheran Care Center--100 LTC Bed Addition, 1986
  - 1554-Apollo Medical Foundation--Rural Health Initiative, 1986
  - 1555-Southeastern Greene Community Health Centers--Continuation Funding, 1986
  - 1556-Alma Illery Medical Center--Competing Renewal Grant Application, 1986
  - 1557-Centerville Clinics--Community Health Center Continuation Funding Grant Application, 1986
  - 1558-Allegheny Health Services--Acquisition of an Additional C.T. Scanner, 1986
  - 1559-Allegheny Health Services--Purchase an MRI Device, 1987
  - 1560-Health Care Development--Purchase an Additional CT Scanner, 1986
  - 1561-Forbes Health System--Cost Overrun Replacement of CT Scanner, 1986 (Box 227)
  - 1562-Allegheny General Hospital--Heart Transplantation Services, 1986
  - 1563-Allegheny General Hospital--Replacement of Linear Accelerator, 1987
  - 1564-Manor Health Care Corporation--120-Bed Leader Nursing and Rehabilitation Facility in Washington County, 1987
  - 1565-Allegheny General Hospital--Conversion of West Allegheny Hospital to Neuropsychiatric Facility, 1987 (Box 228)
  - 1566-Montefiore Hospital, Acquisition of a Dual Energy Linear Accelerator, 1986-1987
  - 1567-Weirton Geriatric Center--Construction of 120-Bed LTC Facility in Washington County, 1986
  - 1568-Dialysis Clinic--Establish an 8-Station Freestanding Dialysis Facility, 1986
  - 1569-Southwest Health System--Unification of Computer Network, 1986
  - 1570-Eye and Ear, Presbyterian-University Hospital, Health Care Division--Construction and Renovation, 1986 (Box 229)
  - 1571-South Hills Health System--Replacement of CT Scanner, 1987 (Box 230)
  - 1572-Children's Hospital of Pittsburgh--Modernization and Renovation, 1987
  - 1573-MRI of Western Pennsylvania--Free-Standing MRI Center, 1986
  - 1574-Ambulatory Health Care Corp--Establish Free-Standing Ambulatory Surgical Facility in Butler County, 1987
  - 1575-Bio-Medical Applications--Establish a 6-Station Dialysis Facility in Armstrong Memorial Hospital, 1987
  - 1576-Southern Allegheny MRI Center-Uptown MRI Associates--Provide MRI Services to Inpatients, 1987
  - 1577-St. Francis Health System--Develop a 150-Bed LTC Facility, 1987
  - 1578-Indiana Hospital--Renovation and Relocation of OB/GYN Unit, 1987
  - 1579-Lawrence County Chapter for Retarded Citizens--8-Bed ICF/MR in New Castle, 1987 (Box 231)
  - 1580-South Side Hospital--Refinance Existing Long-Term Debt, 1987
  - 1581-Suburban General Hospital--Replace Computer System, 1987
  - 1582-Magee Women's Hospital--Replace Data Processing System, 1987
  - 1583-Shannock Valley Area Medical Facility--Rural Health Initiative, 1987
  - 1584-Step-By-Step--Develop Three 8-Bed Facilities, 1987
  - 1585-Northeast Butler County-Community Medical Center--Rural Health Initiative, 1987
  - 1586-Jameson Memorial Hospital--Refinancing of Series A 1985 Hospital Revenue Bonds, 1986
  - 1587-Allegheny General Hospital--8-Station Dialysis Satellite Center in Indiana County, 1987
  - 1588-Sisters of the Order of St. Basil-Mt. Macrina Manor--Additional 66 ICF Beds, 1987
  - 1589-Magee-Women's Hospital--Relocation and Expansion of Ambulatory Care Program, 1987
  - 1590-The Verland Foundation--8-Bed ICF/MR Facility in Fayette County, 1987
  - 1591-South Hills Health System--Refunding of 1975 Series G Hospital Gross Revenue Bonds, 1987
  - 1592-Magee-Women's Hospital--Purchase of Parking Garage, 1987
  - 1593-Washington-Greene Alternative Residential Services--Establish Two 4-Bed ICF/MR Facilities in Washington and Greene Counties, 1987 (Box 232)
  - 1594-Ohio Valley General Hospital--Construction of a Medical Office Building, 1987
  - 1595-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Cost Increase on Stereotactic Radiosurgery with Gamma Knife, 1987
  - 1596-Citizens General Hospital--Advance Refunding of Long Term Debt, 1987
  - 1597-Barr Street Corporation--Establishment of Horizon House, 1987
  - 1598-The Medical Center--Conversion of 34-Bed Medical/Surgical Unit into a 31-Bed Skilled Nursing Unit, 1987
  - 1599-North Hills Passavant Hospital/North Hills Suburban MRI--Provision of MRI Services, 1986
  - 1600-Sidney Square Properties--Construct an 87-Bed Nursing Home on the South Side of Pittsburgh, 1987
  - 1601-The Medical Center--Cost Increase on Cancer Treatment Center, 1987
  - Index Cards for Projects at Hospital Facilities, 1971-1987 (Box 233)
  - Index Cards for Project at Nursing Care Facilities, 1971-1987 (Box 234)